Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Iconographic Collection, 1848-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Thomas Veres Photographs and Negatives, 1963-1996 and undated, (60 boxes)
  - Photographs,1963-1996 and undated
    - 2-1-91. Gary Steele (Box TV30)
    - 2-2-91. Steve Dworin (Box TV30)
    - 2-3-91. Emily Swartzentruber (Box TV30)
    - 2-8-91. Secretaries Day party (Box TV30)
    - 3-9-91. Jerry Dominus (Box TV30)
    - 3-10-91. Mini Golf-Central Park Make A Wish (Box TV30)
    - 3-12-91. Make A Wish check, Kostyra (Box TV30)
    - 4-1,2-91. Bill Gross (Box TV30)
    - 4-3,4-91. Brian Johnson (Box TV30)
    - 4-5-91. Jerry Dominus (Box TV30)
    - 4-6-91. Kelly Clark (Box TV30)
    - 4-7-91. Eyes on Thompson--Miles Colebrook, Allen Thomas (Box TV30)
    - 4-10,11-91. Susan Popper (Box TV30)
    - 4-12,13-91. Bruce Kelly (Box TV30)
    - 4-14,15-91. Mark Messing (Box TV30)
    - 4-16-91. U.S. Marines (Box TV30)
    - 4-22-91. Dennis Kelley studio portrait (Box TV30)
    - 1-1-92. Acc. Management Brian Johnson (Box TV30)
    - 1-2,3-92. Mark Di Massimo Michael Hawkins (Box TV30)
    - 1-4,5-92. Gene Bahr 40th anniversary party (Box TV30)
    - 1-6-92. Children's storefront (Prodigy) (No negatives available) (Box TV30)
    - 1-7-92. Media New Women Santa (Box TV30)
    - 1-9-92. Mark Di Massimo studio portrait (Box TV30)
    - 1-11,12-92. Blood drive I, II (Box TV30)
    - 1-13,14-92. Peter Pavker (Box TV30)
    - 1-15,16-92. Kathy Hassett (Box TV30)
    - 1-17,18-92. Marty Muller (Box TV30)
    - 1-25-92. Errol Morris guest-movie (Box TV30)
    - 1-26-92. United Fund kick-off (Box TV30)
    - 1-27 to 34-92. G. Furgele, A. Gibbons, E. Gildersleeve, A. Himmelstein, K. Junct, L. Kull, C. Lerner, S. Sullivan (Box TV30)
    - 2-4,5-92. Northwest media party (Box TV30)
    - 2-11,12-92. Audrey Himmelstein, Lisa Kull (Box TV30)
    - 2-13-92. Kenneth Walker (Box TV30)
    - 2-14-92. Cindy Lohan (Box TV30)
    - 2-15-92. Bruce Albinson (Box TV30)
    - 2-16-92. Millie Koenig retirement party (Box TV30)
    - 2-20,21-92. Stuart Pearlman (Box TV30)
    - 2-22,23-92. Laura Chesire (Box TV30)
    - 2-24,25-92. Chuck Balestrino (Box TV30)
    - 2-26,27-92. Laura Chesire (Box TV30)
    - 2-28,29-92. Blood drive I, II (Box TV30)
    - 3-1,2-92. Kelly Lowman (Box TV30)
    - 3-3-92. Eyes on Thompson--Kostyra (Box TV30)
    - 3-4-92. Eric Snyder (Box TV31)
    - 3-7 to 17-92. Direct biographicals (Box TV31)
    - 3-19-92. Jim Heekin (Box TV31)
    - 3-20,21,30,31-92. Naomi Schwartz (Box TV31)
    - 3-24-92. Judy Diruzza (Box TV31)
    - 3-25-92. Make A Wish--Central Park (Box TV31)
    - 3-26-92. Group (Direct) Sonya (Box TV31)
    - 3-27,28-92. Izabelle Albaneze (Box TV31)
    - 3-38 to 49-92. Direct biographicals (Box TV31)
    - 4-1-92. Gerry Watson (Box TV31)
    - 4-2,3-92. Media--White Pea Award (Box TV31)
    - 4-6-92. Jane Plant (Box TV31)
    - 4-10,11-92. Jeff Bodenmann (Box TV31)
    - 4-12-92. Tom Groves (Box TV31)
    - 1-1-94. Kelly Clark media party (Box TV31)
    - 1-2 to 13-94. PDP studio portrait brochure (Box TV31)
    - 1-15-94. Christmas party 1993 (Box TV31)
    - 1-16 to 22-94. PDP studio portrait brochure (Box TV31)
    - 1-25,26,27,28-94. Anette Malane, Penny Kowitt, Sandy Chorazy, Nanci Schwartz (Box TV31)
    - 1-29-94. PDP party (Box TV31)
    - 1-30,31-94. Blood drive I, II (Box TV31)
    - 1-32,33,34,35,36,37,38,40-94. New Buisness portraits (Box TV31)
    - 1-42-94. Tutor Juggel (Box TV31)
    - 1-43-94. Producers (Box TV31)
    - 1-44,45-94. Seth Romanon portrait-San Francisco (Box TV31)
    - 1-46-94. Filmmakers (Box TV31)
    - 2-1,2-94. Ignaczio Puccio biographical portrait (Box TV31)
    - 2-1,2-94. Nat Rosen biographical portrait (Box TV31)
    - 2-3,4-94. Charles Generally biographical portrait (Box TV31)
    - 2-3,4,5,6-94. Al Navaro Kathleen Senett, Aaron Simkin, Gina Furgele (Box TV31)
    - 2-5,6-94. Michael Hart biographical portrait (Box TV31)
    - 2-7,8-94. Sue Berkowitz (Box TV31)
    - 2-9-94. Jim Patterson (Box TV31)
    - 2-9,10-94. Richard Di Lallo biographical (Box TV31)
    - 2-11,12-94. Tom Groves portrait (Box TV31)
    - 2-14-94. Secretaries Day (Box TV31)
    - 2-15-94. Bring Your Daughter (Box TV31)
    - 2-17,18-94. Talent show (Box TV31)
    - 2-20-94. Eyes on Thompson--Peter Hughes (Box TV31)
    - 2-21-94. Tutor lunch (Box TV31)
    - 2-22-94. Steve Cody studio portrait (Box TV31)
    - 2-23-94. Irene Hansen (Box TV31)
    - 2-25-94. Malcolm End (Box TV31)
    - 2-26-94. Edward Moed (Box TV31)
    - 2-27,29-94. Marty Rose Award lunch (Grand Hyatt) (Box TV31)
    - 2-29,30-94. Susan Berkowitz portrait (Box TV31)
    - 2-32,33,34-94. Rothann Richert, Emile Council, Cynthia De Rosier (Box TV31)
    - 2-36,37-94. Blood drive I,II (Box TV31)
    - 2-38-94. Mooving party (Box TV31)
    - 3-14-94. Ruthann Richart II biographical (Box TV32)
    - 3-15,16-94. Marty Susz biographical portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-17,18-94. Kelly Clark biographical portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-19,20-94. Manning Rubin biographical. portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-21,22-94. Kendall Crolius biographical. portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-23-94. Michael Hart II biographical (Box TV32)
    - 3-24,25-94. Peter Leinroth biographical. portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-26,27-94. Louis Jones biographical portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-32-94. 420 Lexington 11th floor (Box TV32)
    - 3-33,34,35,36,37-94. Nancy Faua, Amy Rosenberg, R. Richert, Neerja Narayanan, Jim Newell (Box TV32)
    - 3-38-94. Kelly Clark biographical II (Box TV32)
    - 3-39,40-94. Chris DeGuzman biographical portrait B (Box TV32)
    - 3-41,42-94. Kendall Crolius II biographical II portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-43-94. Peter Leinroth biographical II (Box TV32)
    - 3-46-94. Mitch Orfuss: Direct biographical I (Box TV32)
    - 3-48 to 51-94. J. Berman, L. Margulis, I. Baer, Paul Tarantanella (Box TV32)
    - 3-52,53,54-94. Rob Santangelo I, Rob Santangelo II, Susan Sullivan (Box TV32)
    - 3-55,56-94. Make-A-Wish (Box TV32)
    - 3-57-94. Eyes on Thompson--Jerry Dominic (Box TV32)
    - 3-58-94. Direct group (summer outings) (Box TV32)
    - 3-59-94. Alan Goltz studio portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-60,61-94. Jean Brown studio portrait, Ashley Adams studio portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-62-94. Barbara Singer New Business portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-64,65-94. Nancy Hallberg biographical portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-66,67-94. Kathy Stevens biographical portrait (Box TV32)
    - 3-68-94. Serge Karamanoukian New Business studio portrait (Box TV32)
    - 4-1-94. Mitch Orfuss: Direct biographical II (Box TV32)
    - 4-2-94. Eyes on Thompson--London: Jasper Shelbourne, Dominic Procter (Box TV32)
    - 4-3-94. Jim Foster (magazine) (Box TV32)
    - 4-7,8-94. YMCA Emily Schwartzenruber, Ron Burns (Box TV32)
    - 4-9-94. Larry Volpi studio portrait (Box TV32)
    - 4-10,11-94. New V.P. party (Box TV32)
    - 4-12,13,14,15-94. Annette Stover, May Armstrong, Carrie Craglyaile, Debbie Kowarz (Box TV32)
    - 4-16-94. Domingo Perez Senior V.P (Box TV32)
    - 4-18-94. Michael Hawkins--Direct (Box TV32)
    - 4-19-94. Warner-Lambert International group (Box TV32)
    - 4-21-94. Salvador Dali art (Box TV32)
    - 1-6-95. Margaret Bambakas,Linda Rovero, Andrea Lando: group Marty Susz (Box TV32)
    - 1-7,8-95. Volutair Christmas party (Box TV32)
    - 1-9 to 31-95. PDP portrait brochure (Box TV32)
    - 1-32-95. PDP NIT (Box TV32)
    - 1-33-95. Blood drive (Box TV32)
    - 1-35-95. Barry Lott portrait (Box TV32)
    - 1-36-95. Jean Pool portrait (Box TV32)
    - 1-37,38,39-95. John Clinton biographical portrait (Box TV32)
    - 1-41-95. Bell Atlantic group (Box TV32)
    - 1-42-95. Kodak group (Atrium) color (Box TV32)
    - 1-44-95. Scott International meeting (Box TV32)
    - 1-46-95. Domingo Perez portrait (Box TV32)
    - 1-47-95. Gail Heany portrait (Box TV32)
    - 1-48-95. Tony Incaltera New Business portrait (Box TV32)
    - 1-49-95. John Mossawr New Business portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-50-95. Karen Prober New Business portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-51-95. United Fund kickoff party (Box TV33)
    - 2-2-95. Janine Prestegaard portrait (Box TV33)
    - 2-3,4-95. Secretaries Day (Box TV33)
    - 2-5-95. Bob Schrijuer portrait (Box TV33)
    - 2-7-95. Tutor--chorus (Box TV33)
    - 2-8,9-95. RSVP Tavern on the G: Janine Prestegaard (Box TV33)
    - 2-10-95. Maria Gianoutsos portrait (Box TV33)
    - 2-11-95. Jolie Defeis portrait (Box TV33)
    - 2-12-95. David May portrait (Box TV33)
    - 2-13-95. John Pearson studio portrait (Box TV33)
    - 2-14-95. Mark Fenske studio portrait (Box TV33)
    - 2-15,16-95. Blood drive I, II (Box TV33)
    - 3-1-95. Corporate running group (Box TV33)
    - 3-3-95. James Vincent portrait (Box TV33)
    - 3-4-95. Midge Kyler portrait (Box TV33)
    - 3-5-95. Kellog breakfast (Box TV33)
    - 3-6-95. Susaan Machtiger portrait (Box TV33)
    - 3-8-95. Laura Katz portrait (Box TV33)
    - 3-9 to 17-95. Weight Watchers: Jane Plant, Paul Salisbury, Gina Battafaco, Leann Davis, Evelyn Joice, Linda Goldstein, Allison Rosenberg, Megwin Finegan, Heidi Young (Box TV33)
    - 3-19-95. Eyes on Thompson--Jerry Dominus (Box TV33)
    - 3-20,21,22,23-95. Heinekin: Adam Kanner, Matt Dowsher, Karen Prober, Karin Kaplan (Box TV33)
    - 3-24,25-95. Make-A-Wish Central Park (Box TV33)
    - 3-27-95. Heineken decorations (Box TV33)
    - 4-1,2-95. Ron Capello, Denis Riney (Box TV33)
    - 4-3-95. Liz Coples portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-4-95. Claudia Rose portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-6,7-95. De Beers 420 LES offices with people (Box TV33)
    - 4-9,10-95. Water Cooler Still Comp (Box TV33)
    - 4-13,14-95. Young Creatives with Susan Giannino (Box TV33)
    - 4-15-95. Tom Ferrara portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-17-95. Jeff De Joseph portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-18-95. Brad Mintz portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-19-95. Nat Rosen party (Box TV33)
    - 4-20-95. Rick Glickman portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-21-95. Michael Gross portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-23-95. Lynn Diamond (Box TV33)
    - 4-24-95. Walter Ife portrait (Box TV33)
    - 4-25-95. Bryan Johnston portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-1-96. Dororthy Marcus (Box TV33)
    - 1-2-96. Christmas party 1995 (Box TV33)
    - 1-4-96. Richard Pollet portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-5,6-96. De Beers Bart Boydston studio portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-7,8-96. Ron Dean studio portrait, De Beers (Box TV33)
    - 1-9,10-96. De Beers, Pat Henneberly studio portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-11,12-96. Barbara Hatht studio portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-13-96. Bob Verbeck VP studio portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-14-96. Chris Vilante VP studio portrait (Box TV33)
    - 1-15,16-96. Blood drive I, II (Box TV33)
    - 1-18-96. Rona Oberman, Partner (Box TV33)
    - 1-19-96. Bob Shea, Partner (Box TV33)
    - 1-20,21-96. Kathy Beall portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-22,23-96. Preston Foy portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-24,25-96. Bob Wheeler portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-26,27-96. Gene Laroff portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-28,29-96. Rachel Rosin (Box TV34)
    - 1-30-96. Kellog international meeting (Box TV34)
    - 1-31-96. Peter Geary, Partner (Box TV34)
    - 1-32-96. Stacy Style, Partner studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-33-96. Liza Stein studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-36-96. PDP brochure (Box TV34)
    - 1-57,58-96. PDP party (Box TV34)
    - 1-60-96. United Fund party (Box TV34)
    - 1-61-96. Lucy Purdy portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-62-96. Jill Kossoff portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-63-96. Judy Ritensky (Box TV34)
    - 1-64-96. Wess Matt portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-65-96. Kurt Meinen portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-66-96. John Zissmos portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-67-96. Gina Moorhead studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-68-96. Gina Furgele studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-69-96. Audrey Delgrosso studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-72-96. Anne Wilson studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-70-96. Alberto Ferrer studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-71-96. Linda Goldstein studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-73-96. James Kloiber studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 1-74-96. Kristin Paulus studio portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-1-96. Tim Thom portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-2-96. Sheryl Max portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-3,4,5,6-96. Laura Bowning, Michelle Carabello, Kenel Restiro, Elaine Kim (Box TV34)
    - 2-7-96. Norm Macmaster portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-8-96. Connie Maloy portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-9-96. Sheryl Prince (Box TV34)
    - 2-10-96. Nancy Faua (Box TV34)
    - 2-11-96. Bill Treuedi (Box TV34)
    - 2-12-96. Sue Bernard (Box TV34)
    - 2-13-96. Eillen Lyons (Box TV34)
    - 2-14-96. Maria Feigenson (Box TV34)
    - 2-15-96. Lee Margolis (Box TV34)
    - 2-16-96. David Sciascia II portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-17-96. Ayn Bree Sheahan (Box TV34)
    - 2-18,19-96. Secretaries Day (Box TV34)
    - 2-20-96. Debeers breakfast (Box TV34)
    - 2-21-96. Evelyn Joyce portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-22-96. Jennifer Wishnie portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-23-96. Neeraja Nadayanan portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-24-96. Rob Rothschild (Box TV34)
    - 2-25-96. Orielle Duval (Box TV34)
    - 2-26-96. Andrea Halbersadt portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-27-96. Rachel Treitelman-Rosin portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-28-96. Lynn Diamond portrait, De Beers (Box TV34)
    - 2-29-96. David Sciascia biographical portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-30-96. Connie Marsala portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-31-96. Christine Hoffman portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-32-96. Jason Valentias portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-33-96. Tom O'Connel portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-34-96. Victoria Brown (Box TV34)
    - 2-35-96. Eloisa Pena portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-36-96. Joe Pantigoso portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-37-96. Karen Silverstein portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-38-96. Biographical studio portrait Angela Saunders (Box TV34)
    - 2-39-96. Brad Mintz for magazine (Box TV34)
    - 2-40-96. Rachel Rosen studio portrait Debeers (Box TV34)
    - 2-41-96. Vincent Genn portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-42-96. Mai Lissa Armstrong portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-44-96. Wendy Harrington portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-45-96. Kathryn Schaub portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-48-96. Susan Charbonfau portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-49-96. Paul Trantanella portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-50-96. Kenny Ho portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-51-96. Linda Clasen portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-53-96. Gina Furgele portrait (Box TV34)
    - 2-54-96. Michael Hawkins portrait (Box TV35)
    - 2-55-96. Scott Hennley portrait (Box TV35)
    - 2-56-96. Lisa Micarelli (Box TV35)
    - 2-57-96. Peter Pauker portrait (Box TV35)
    - 2-58,59-96. Blood drive I, II (Box TV35)
    - 2-60-96. Hush Puppy (Box TV35)
    - 2-61-96. Melissa Murphy, Burt Manning (Box TV35)
    - 3-2-96. Vicki Brown portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-4-96. Tom Ferrara portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-5-96. Audrey DelGrosso portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-6-96. State of the Company (Box TV35)
    - 3-8-96. Warner Lambert international group (Box TV35)
    - 3-9-96. Debbie Reiner studio portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-10-96. Emilie Council portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-11-96. James Tan portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-12-96. Linda Classen portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-13-96. Phil Welsher portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-14-96. Chris Seid portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-15-96. Andrew Fenning studio portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-16-96. Sheron Slater portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-17-96. Jaleh Iranpour studio portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-18,19-96. Schick party (Box TV35)
    - 3-21-96. Bonnie Mayo portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-22-96. Susan Rizack portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-23-96. Chelsea Chan portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-24-96. Jim Kloiber Direct biographical (Box TV35)
    - 3-25-96. Rae Loesch Direct biographical (Box TV35)
    - 3-26-96. PDP group 28 Prints (Box TV35)
    - 3-27-96. Sheron Slater portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-27-96. Shelley Broder (Box TV35)
    - 3-28-96. Debbie Curtis studio portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-29-96. John Haskin portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-30-96. Debra Coughlin portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-31-96. Shelly Wattson portrait (Box TV35)
    - 3-32-96. Gina Botafuco portrait Direct (Box TV35)
    - 4-1-96. Phillip Conklin portrait (Box TV35)
    - 4-4-96. Chris Soares Portrait (Box TV35)
    - 4-8-96. Still life Debeers (Box TV35)
    - 4-9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16-96. Scott Keegal, Stuart Keating, Stuart Burkhoff, Kurt Meinen, John Haskin, Barry Shelbourn, Bonnie Mayo, Judy Ritensky (Box TV35)
    - 4-17,18,19-96. Amie Stern, Tim Kane, Stark Kalten (Box TV35)
    - 4-21-96. Health Fair (Box TV35)
    - 4-20,22-96. Entertainment Tonight (Box TV35)
  - Negatives, 1963-1996 and undated>
    - No job number. 9th-floor receptionists (Box TV36)
    - No job number. 11th-floor receptionists (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Art exhibition II--unidentified (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Basketball team: team and action shots (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Baxter, Clayton, Rost (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Big conference room rebuilding (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Blackhouse boutique (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Brasil Manager (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Burry--Channel 13 story (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Calcutta Manager (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Direct Mail group (Box TV36)
    - No job number. East Harlem Children--Red Onion (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Ethikos press conference (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Ford group (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Ford meeting Hotel Commodore, group action shots (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Ford Motor Company: photographs of printed pages re. 1962 Ford, 1964 Ford (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Ford showroom with cars and people 1965 Fords (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Forum group (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Fran Wood: Debbie______Miss America studio and ______village, China Tour (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Frozen food group lunch (Box TV36)
    - No job number. ____and JWT (Box TV36)
    - No job number. girls exercise story (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Girls softball--Central Park (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Girls softball trophy (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Group in Board of Directors room, Denmark-Sutton, Mr. Parild (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Henry Wood, Tom Fucigna (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Hotel Roosevelt retiring man and secretary (Box TV36)
    - No job number. International Managers meeting (Box TV36)
    - No job number. J. Walter meeting (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Joan Wood--Kodak pinhole camera, boy in studio and U.N (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Joan Wood--playcard on location (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Kitchen story (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Kodak meeting (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Lunch--Mr. Strouse, Mr. Wilson, Mr. White, Mr. Gustave Van Rieman--Belgium (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Lunch (Seibert) Bernice Fitzgibond (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Lynda Confessori--Kodak Academy (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Masterpiece pipe tobacco--4 men (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Mayor of Anchorage, Alaska (Jack Mangan) (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Miss. Florence Reesek, Mr. White (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Mr. Fisher and Mr. Higgbie (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Mr. Seymour press conference (Youth Now) (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Mr. Strouse--Australian book donation (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Mr Strouse and client (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Mr Strouse--public library (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Mr. Strouse receives award from the Hundred Year Association of NY (Box TV36)
    - No job number. New Room with two way mirror (Box TV36)
    - No job number. New York World's Fair poster contest (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Norman Strouse greets new JWT President Dan Seymour (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Pan Am cocktail party (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Paycheck line (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Purotier team group (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Reader's Digest contest winners--Wally Elton in photographs (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Receptionists story (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Secretaries story (Box TV36)
    - No job number. ____ ASS-- John Rost group (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Singer account (no photographs available) (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Singer machine 1850--experimental (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Singer--Ted______ (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Singer--Sheron, vacuum cleaner on location (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Softball team (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Ted Royal receives Strouse Award at Astoria Hotel (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Ted Royal with art (no photographs available) (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Television news story (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Tom O'Brien--London--NY, Congoleum (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Tom Paine--puppets (Box TV36)
    - No job number. T.V. shop (Box TV36)
    - No job number. UN luncheon II (Box TV36)
    - No job number. U.N. luncheon in Colonial dining room (Box TV36)
    - No job number. Unidentified man (no photographs available) (Box TV36)
    - No job number. U.S. Marine Corps--St. Patricks Day prank (Box TV36)
    - No job number. W. German--guests Hotel New Yorker (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Art exhibit (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Art show, art floor (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Board of Directors group portrait in front of Stanley Resor portrait (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Brillo meeting (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Christmas chorus-staff in choir robes, Norman Strouse, LP recording (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Computer room (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Computer room and Dr. Sondar (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Ford meeting (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Ford: New Mustang model (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Ford store sign: Our hot cakes are selling like Mustangs (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Ford team group shots and print ads for 1965 Fords (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Henry Schacte (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Interview--unidentified women (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Italian newspaperman (no photographs available) (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Irving Trust Company--Silver Bowl Commemorating JWT centennial (no photographs available) (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. J. Walter Executive offices with unidentified people (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Japan Art Directors--Tom Yamada (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. JWT Centennial medal, 1964 (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. JWT Centennial mug (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. JWT Co. 19th-century promotional items--property of Norman Strouse (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. JWT colonial dining room (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Lever: a Philippine Lux starlet (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Library (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. Men's softball team (Box TV36)
    - 1963-64. New York World's Fair--brochure, unidentified head shots (no photographs available) (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. New York World's Fair--photographs for brochure, unidentified visitors (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. New York World's Fair site and meetings (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Norman Rockwell painting of Howard Kohl in office (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Norman Strouse and others (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Norman Strouse and unidentified Salvation Army man (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Norman Strouse, Esther Peterson including some photographs in JWT colonial dining room (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Putting up art exhibit (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Statue (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Television filming--Ted Royal, Jack Mangem, Terry T.V. girl (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. William Peniche, Eduardo Criado (Box TV37)
    - 1963-64. Women--eye makeup demonstration (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Art exhibition (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Awards meeting, 1966 (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Awards--studio still comp (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Baseball team, 1966 (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. basketball team (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Basketball team, 967 (Box TV37)
    - 1956-66. Bearded JWT people (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Bill Yurdije--Blue Shield and Blue Cross (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Board of Directors Meeting Seymour Strouse (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Bowling team (Box TV37)
    - 1965-66. Brillo meeting II (Box TV37)